Contact

christopher.gargala@outlook .com

www.linkedin.com/in/christophergargala (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Leadership Healthcare Management Critical Care

Certifications

Certified Change Management Practitioner Informatics Nursing (RN-BC) BLS CCRN

Christopher Gargala

MSN, RN-BC, CCRN

Indianapolis, Indiana

Summary

Experienced Clinical Manager with a demonstrated history of healthcare leadership in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Leadership, Nursing Management, Workflow Analysis, Change Management, Patient Flow, Healthcare Technologies and Nursing Process. Dedicated healthcare services professional with a Masters of Nursing Leadership and Management focused in Nursing Administration from The George Washington University.

Experience

Indiana University Health
Clinical IS-Implementation Manager
June 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months)
Indianapolis, Indiana

MedStar Georgetown University Hospital 6 years 10 months

Clinical Nurse Manager November 2015 - May 2018 (2 years 7 months)

Clinical Administrator February 2015 - November 2015 (10 months)

Clinical Nurse August 2011 - March 2015 (3 years 8 months)

University of Michigan Health System Nurse Assistant 2009 - 2011 (2 years)

Education

The George Washington University

Master of Nursing Leadership and Management, Nursing Administration

University of Michigan

Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse